http://www.wwoz.org/wwozorg-privacy-policy

Listen Now
On Air:
Listen Now
On Air:
WWOZ.org - Privacy Policy
WWOZ 90.7FM ("WWOZ") has created this privacy policy (the "Policy") so you will understand when and how personal information is collected, used, disclosed and protected with respect to our Web site www.wwoz.org (the "Site"). By accessing our Site and submitting information to us, you consent to the privacy practices described in this Policy, as modified from time to time by us.
Information About You:
We collect two basic types of information from our Site; namely, personal information and aggregate information. Personal information is information that is directly associated with a specific person, such as your name, address, telephone number, billing information, or e-mail address, or information about activities that are directly linked to a specific person.
Our definition of personal information does not include "aggregate" information. Aggregate information is data we collect about a group or category of users from which individual identities have been removed. Aggregate data may include anonymous demographic information such as country of origin, citizenship, ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, submission and survey information. In other words, how you use our Site may be collected and combined with information about how others use the Site, but no personal information will be included in the resulting data. Aggregate data helps us understand trends and user needs so that we can better consider new services or tailor our existing offerings to user desires. An example of aggregate data is a report that shows how frequently and how long a webcast has been accessed. The report would not contain any personal information, but the aggregate data might be purchased by or shared with a third party such as one of our licensors.
Here are the types of personal and other information we collect. You should refer to the rest of this Policy to see how we use, disclose and protect this information:
Information You Give Us:
We collect information you give us when you register for or use our Service, or post information on the Site. Examples include the following:
Donation/Purchase Information:
When you make a donation on our Site, we may collect various kinds of information about you, including your name, e-mail address, credit card information, your employer, home and business addresses, and home and business phone numbers. In the event that WWOZ offers products for sale online, when you make purchases from the Site, we may collect purchasing information such as product orders and shipping address(es), and payment information.
Submissions:
From time-to-time we may post surveys on the Site. The surveys may request demographic information and customer feedback. Participation in these requests is completely voluntary, and with each request you will have the choice of whether or not to participate and disclose information. Such survey information will be used to improve the overall experience on our Site. Also, we may collect information that identifies you personally when you submit comments, questions or suggestions to our customer service department.
Public Forums:
WWOZ may offer online chat rooms, discussion boards, online forums, blogs and other interactive technologies that allow individual comments and messages to be tied to a user's name or e-mail address. Any information you post in such forums is public information. We cannot control what uses third parties may make of personal information you share in such forums.
Automatically Collected Information:
We automatically receive certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, when you visit the Site, our systems automatically collect your IP address and the type of browser you use. Information may be automatically collected through the use of "cookies" which are discussed in more detail below. We also collect various types of "clickstream" information, which is information about your browsing behavior, such as IP address information, entry and exit points for the Site, webcasts or playlists accessed, and page views and impressions.
Information About Children:
We do not knowingly, directly or passively, collect information from children under the age of 13. If we create offers and products that make it appropriate to collect information from children under the age of 13, we will notify you of the change in this Policy. We also will ask a parent to confirm his/her consent in advance of any collection, use or disclosure of that information.
Use of "Cookies"
Cookies are small text files placed on your hard drive by a Web site when you visit. These files identify your computer and record your preferences and other data about your visit so that, when you return to the site, the site knows who you are and can personalize your visit. In general, we use cookies to collect information so that we can determine how to improve the Site by seeing which areas, features and products are most popular; to personalize the Site, make recommendations based on content you have liked in the past, and otherwise to improve the overall site experience; and to complete transactions you have requested. In the event we permit third parties to advertise on our Site, advertisers that serve ads on our Site may also use their own cookies. Such outside cookies are governed by the privacy policies of the entities placing the ads, and are not subject to this Policy.
Most browsers automatically accept cookies as the default setting. You should be able to modify the setting of your browser to reject cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the sites you visit by editing browser options. If you decide not to accept our cookies, you will still be able to access those parts of our site available to the general public, but you may not be able to use some of the site's features or services and you may have a less satisfactory experience.
As technology advances and cookies provide more functionality, we expect to utilize them in different offerings in different ways. As we do so, this Policy will be updated to provide you with more information.
USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
Internal Use of Personal Information
In general, we use personal information internally to serve our users and to enhance and extend our relationship with our users. For example, by understanding how you use the Site from your computer, we are able to customize and personalize your experience. More specifically, we use personal information for donation purposes, to complete transactions you have requested, to anticipate and resolve problems with our Site, to respond to customer support inquiries, and to create and inform you of new products or services from WWOZ or others that better meet your needs. You should review the following section to understand when we disclose personal information to third parties.
Disclosure of Personal Information
We will not trade, share or sell a donor's personal information with anyone else, nor send donor mailings on behalf of other organizations, except as described in the specific circumstances below.
Your Consent:
We will disclose personal information with your consent, which we may obtain in writing, verbally, through online means or as part of a separate agreement. If new services are offered in the future that require disclosure of personal information to third parties or other uses of personal information not covered in this Policy, we will update this Policy to reflect the changes.
Transaction Processing:
We disclose personal information to third parties as necessary to complete a transaction you have requested (such as donations) or to perform a service on our behalf. When a third party acts solely on our behalf, we will require it to follow our privacy practices.
Internal Analysis:
We may use information about you for our own internal statistical, design or operational purposes, such as to estimate our audience size, measure aggregate traffic patterns, and understand demographic, customer interest, purchasing and other trends among our users. We may outsource these tasks to third parties, provided the use and disclosure of your personal information by these third parties is restricted to performance of these tasks.
Protection of WWOZ and Others:
We release personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law (e.g., a lawful subpoena, warrant or court order); to enforce or apply our policies; to initiate, render, bill, and collect for amounts owed to us; to protect our rights or property, or to protect our users from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful use of our Site; or if we reasonably believe that an emergency involving immediate danger of death or serious physical injury to any person requires disclosure of communications or justifies disclosure of records without delay.
THIRD-PARTY SITES
Please be aware that we provide links to third-party Web sites from the Site as a service to our guests and we are not responsible for the content or information collection practices of those sites. For example, if you take advantage of services or products offered on one of these Web sites, the information you submit will be subject to its privacy policy, not this one. The privacy policies of third-party Web sites will differ from those of WWOZ. Therefore, we encourage you to review and understand their privacy policies before providing them with information.
UPDATING THIS POLICY
We will revise and update this Policy if our practices change, as technology changes, or as we add new services or change existing ones. If we make any material changes to the Policy or to how we handle your personal information, we will post an "update" notice to the Site and change the date of the Policy. You should refer back to this page for the latest information.
CONTACTING US
If you have any questions, comments or concerns about this Policy, please contact wwoz@wwoz.org. Or you can send mail to: WWOZ, 1008 N. Peters, New Orleans, LA 70116.
Topic tags: Website
Get the 'OZone monthly newsletter
Follow 'OZ
Get the 'OZone monthly newsletter
Subscribe
Like us on Facebook
Learn More
Like us on Facebook
Hear it here!
Listen
Listen Live!
Donate Now!
All user-submitted content owned by the Poster.
Everything else is (C) 2001-2020 WWOZ New Orleans 90.7 FM.
All rights reserved.
